They'd bust your head just for the hell of it. So
think what they'd do for $500,000!
The Squeeze is a thriller, crime film directed by Michael Apted.
An alcoholic London ex-cop becomes involved in a kidnapping drama and tries
to free the daughter of a friend from a brutal gangster mob.
Jim Naboth, played by Stacy Keach.
Keith, played by David Hemmings.
Foreman, played by Edward Fox.
Vic, played by Stephen Boyd.
Jill, played by Carol White.
Teddy, played by Freddie Starr.
The Squeeze is a 1977 British gangster thriller directed by Michael Apted and
starring Stacy Keach, Edward Fox, David Hemmings and Stephen Boyd.
It was based on the 1974 novel Whose Little Girl Are You?
by Bill James (as David Craig).
The screenplay was by Minder creator Leon Griffiths.
The tone is dark and intense.